(Bernadette:)Well, we didn't exactly decide.
(Bernadette:)We were talking about it,
(Bernadette:)and then one night
we got a little reckless.
Oh, tell us!
Yeah, tell us.
(Bernadette:)No, I'm embarrassed.
Oh, come on,
(Penny:)we're all grown-ups.
We've all done it.
Me! Me-me, too!
I'm a grown-up and I've done it!
(Leonard:)Fine.
(Bernadette:)We were out one night,
(Bernadette:)and things got
a little spontaneous.
(Amy:)Oh, that sounds juicy.
(Bernadette:)Well, Sheldon was going on
and on about time zones
(Bernadette:)and railroad schedules,
and I went out...
(Penny:)Wait, I remember that.
Hang on.
(Penny:)You did it
at our place?
(Bernadette:)Kind of on Sheldon's bed.
What?!
No!
(Bernadette:)I was headed to the bathroom,
(Bernadette:)and I passed Howie
on his way out.
(Bernadette:)Usually he says,
"Do not go in there,"
(Bernadette:)but this time he said,
"Hey, let's go in here."
(Amy:)How could you do that?
I'm sorry,
(Bernadette:)but you know what it's like
when you're with your man